Hello friends, Namaskar, I am Ken Raturi, Chief
Life Insurance
Advisor and Certified Financial Planner,
AMFI. I welcome you to today's video.
Today I have made this video with a special purpose.
Through this video, I
want to tell all my friends that there are
many risks in our life, out of which
health is also a major risk,
so for this it is very important for us to get health insurance.
Many of you must have got health insurance,
but today's topic is that the
best plan in the market today,
ICICI Lombard
Insurance Company has launched a health insurance
plan named Elevate. Elevate's
special purpose is that firstly, the
cashless availability in it is cashless anyway.
If we face
any medical problem and we are
not able to go to a network hospital,
we want to get ourselves treated by a knowledgeable doctor in a good hospital near us,
then under this plan, you can get this
insurance in cashless form
in any hospital. The only condition is
that at the time of admission,
you just have to inform the company's toll free number 24 hours before that.  If
this is a problem and we are getting
admitted in this hospital, within 24 hours
the company will convert it into cashless treatment
and your treatment will be done cashless there also.
Secondly, the best thing in this is
infighting
care, which means that
if a huge claim comes in during the entire policy term, no matter of what the
amount is, then that claim is also
settled by the company and it is paid.
Thirdly, what is there in this, there is
unlimited restoration, if ever our sum assured is
spent completely in a single illness
and we need it again, then the
company restores it and
we can take advantage of that also. Thirdly, the
main thing in this is that there is a
health booster option in this. Health booster
means that if we take a time shot policy at any time
and we have
opted for health booster in it, then that time shot will keep
doubling every year. Suppose today
we are taking a policy of Rs 10 lakh, then next
year it will be Rs 20 lakh, then Rs 30 lakh, then Rs 40 lakh, whether there is a
claim in it or not.  There is no no claim bonus,
this is a health booster. This health
booster will continue in it and it will be available in
it till an unlimited amount. So I
request everyone that you should
think seriously about health insurance
and take health insurance in ICICI
Lombard
Elite Elevate sorry Elevate plan
and
secure your family and what
I would say is that sometimes unexpected
expenses that may come upon us suddenly should be
covered. I have also taken my plan
from there and it is very good. Even recently
my wife's claim also came, which the
company settled very easily.
For claim renewal and other things, the company has
a mobile app called Il Tech Care. You
can also renew the policy from there and if any
claim comes, we
can register the claim there also. So take advantage of the new age
plan which I am telling you about.
If you
want to know anything more about this plan, then please
check and call me. I will happily
help you. Thank you very much.
Hello.